Stephanie Arteaga

Communication Design Student
Computer Science Minor
811 Wawona St
Manteca, California 95337
(209) 624-9670
starteaga@csumb.edu

SKILLS

I am a creative and innovative individual with three years of experience in retail focusing on customer engagement and sales. I am able to learn quickly, a problem solver, and overall, a team player. I have knowledge in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.

EXPERIENCE

Target Corporations, Manteca, California - Beauty Team Expert

SEPTEMBER 2018 - CURRENT

- Beauty Team Member 2018-2019
 - Focused on specialty sales and interacted with guests in the cosmetic, haircare, and skincare departments.
 - Established a relationship with customers and engaged with products and services.
 - Hosted sampling events to promote new products and build customer's beauty regimen.
 - Managed the stocking of products, product replenishment, and maintained store cleanliness.
- Beauty Team Expert 2019-currently
 - o Became a trainer and brand owner for the Beauty Department.
 - Helped remodel Target store when under construction and set up new model.
 - Focused on remerchandising products and product markdowns.
 - Scheduling new product sets (store end caps, new displays, new branding).

EDUCATION

- Sierra High School, Manteca, CA August 2014 May 2018
 - o `High School Diploma
- San Joaquin Delta College, Stockton, CA August 2018 May 2021
 - Associates Degree in Interdisciplinary Studies
- CSU Monterey Bay, Seaside, CA Currently

AWARDS

Adobe Certified Associate in Visual Design Using Adobe Photoshop